PEDRO MEDINA ROBLES

COMPUTER SYSTEMS ENGINEER

PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATE: 13260429

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

PHP (OOP)

Composer

JAVA

MySQL

MariaDB

jSON

GIT

UML HTML5, JS

CSS3 AVANZADO

AJAX

jQuery

WebApps (Angular)

Bootstrap

Visual Basic.Net (Windows Forms)

Windows Server, Linux Server

PERSONAL SKILLS

Creative

Organized

Results oriented

Tenacious

Patient

CONTACT

9371678906

pedro.medina.ro97@outlook.com

Col. Tascoob Street River Mezcalapa

Block 3 #8

CP.86500, H.Cárdenas, Tabasco

GitHub; PedroMedina97

OTHER ABILITIES

TECHNICAL SUPPORT FOR

COMPUTER EQUIPMENT

-NETWORKS

-SERVERS

-MICROSOFT OFFICE COMPLETE

-PHOTOSHOP, ILLUSTRATOR,

PREMIERE PRO (BASIC)

IDIOMAS

English B2 conversational

COURSES | TRAININGS

BOOTSTRAP

UDEMY

<u>PHP</u>

UDEMY

JAVASCRIPT, NODE JS, ANGULAR, JQUERY

JDEMY

ABOUT ME

I am a Computer Systems Engineer graduated from the Universidad del Valle de Mexico, I have worked on projects in the corporate sector, oil, automotive, agricultural and recently administrative accounting integrating map technologies, REDUX patterns, Angular, PHP, Node.js so my skills are of a Full Stack Developer, but I can perform without problems as Back End or Front End.

EXPERIENCE

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

KOUD | August. 2023 - August. 2024

FIGMA-based Template Development

API web services consumption

Development of re-usable components in ANGULAR

REDUX

CSS and SCSS animation development

Maps (Leaflet)

Bootstrap, Materialize

KANBAN, DevOps, Agile, SCRUM

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING ASSISTANT

IPS GROUP | FEBRUARY. 2022 - MARCH. 2023

Development and consumption of REST API services (PHP)

Library integration (Composer)

Databases (MySQL, MariaDB)

Front-End Development (Angular, jQuery)
Technical support to internal and remote users

Process improvement

Planning with Microsoft Project, SCRUM, Jira Software

PROJECT LEADER / JUNIOR PROGRAMMER

Xinergia Group | NOVIEMBRE 2019 - ENERO. 2022

Overall project management using agile methodologies (SCRUM)

Project and deliverables planning with Microsoft Project

Dashboard management

Analyzing and documenting information from client minutes

Use of digital communication and file transfer tools

Relational database modeling

Design of process, flow and UML diagrams

Web design (Angular Framework, Bootstrap)

API's development and integration

EDUCATION

COMPUTER SYSTEMS ENGINEERING

Universidad del Valle de México | 2016 - 2021